Okay, so now that traffic is looking pretty good and there's no designs by jet, but we have two problems
with cars.
Firstly, so the traffic is weighted at a very crazy enough rate.
Like again you see this just one car.
Next car and the next car and so on.
And they should spawn at different rates.
And secondly, all the same car.
And if you look at the costumes you can see we have multiple different car types.
So this is your mini challenge.
I want you to try and solve both these problems.
Firstly making the car spawn at different rates, then having them be different cars.
So come on, you can do this.
Pause the video now and give this little mini challenge a shot.
Well, did you work it out?
If you haven't worked it out yet, it's all to do with random numbers.
And let me show you what I mean.
So firstly, to get the car spawning speed to vary, all we need to do is drag a pick random into this
weight block, and here we can have it vary from 0.6 seconds to 1.2 seconds.
And if we hit play, you can see that it looks a lot less robotic and a bit more natural.
Finally, to make it look less like the cars are coming off a factory line and more like normal traffic.
Here we can use costumes.
So going into the looks and then adding this switch costume right to the start of our script, we can
have a change.
You see from if you click on here we have six different car costumes.
And here again we can also add a pick random.
And because we have six costumes we can pick a random one between 1 and 6.
Now when we hit play, well, that looks a lot better.
It's actually starting to look like a proper game.
So great work so far.